Guide to the Carolyn Caddes papers and photographs, circa 1980-2015
Stanford University Libraries.
- Series 3: California Winemakers (Acc # 2004- 091), 1982- 1993
  - Amerine, Maynard, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of correspondence between Carolyn Caddes and Dr. Maynard Amerine and a copy of California Wine Industry Oral History Project. The section is entitled “The University of California and the State’s Wine Industry” and is an interview conducted by Ruth Teiser. Copyright 1972. Also included are prints and negatives of Amerine’s portrait session with Caddes.
  - Brother Timothy, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of a copy of California Wine Industry Oral History Project entitled “Brother Timothy: The Christian Brothers as Winemakers”. Also included is correspondence between Caddes and Brother Timothy and prints of their portrait session.
  - Business cards, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of business cards from different wineries, photographers and businesses in Napa Valley.
  - Chavez, Cesar, 1992- 1993
    The materials consist of letters written to Chavez and research.
  - Davies, Jack, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of negative, prints, informational brochures on Scramsberg winery, an issue of Food and Wine and correspondence.
  - Fromm, Alfred, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of correspondence, and a copy of California Wine Industry Oral History Project section entitled “Alfred Fromm: Marketing California Wine and Brandy”.
  - Gallo, Ernest, 1992- 1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of correspondence, prints and copies of portraits.
  - Gallo family clippings, 1992- 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of clippings about the Gallo family and Napa Valley.
  - Gallo, Julio: correspondence, 1992- 1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of correspodence between Julio Gallo and Caddes and occassionally Lorraine Jones, Julio's assistant.
  - Gallo, Julio: notes and writing, 1992- 1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of notes from Caddes' interactions with Julio. Also included are drafts of an article written by Caddes entitled "Julio Gallo: A First and Last Visit".
  - Gallo, Julio: photographs, 1992- 1993 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    The materials consist of prints and copies from the portrait session.
  - Gomberg, Louis, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Grgich, Miljenko, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    The materials consist of correspondence, information about Grgich Hills Cellar and prints and negatives from the portrait session.
  - Heitz, Joseph, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of clippings, correspondence, winery information and notes.
  - Jackson, Jess, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of a letter to Jess Jackson.
  - Martini, Louis, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of negatives, prints, informational brochures about the Louis M. Martini Winery, correspondence and clippings.
  - Mondavi, Robert, 1992- 1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of correspondence, prints and photographs from portrait session, clippings and a copy of California Wine Industry Oral History Project section entitled “Robert Mondavi: Creativity in the California Wine Industry”.
  - Olmo, Harold, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of correspondence to Harold Olmo.
  - Portraits of Success: California wine makers book project files, 1992- 1993 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of notes. correspondence, a book proposal, reciepts and lists for the book project.
  - Research clippings, 1992- 1993 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of clippings on Napa Valley and California wine makers.
  - Research: correspondence, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of correspondence about ideas for a new book about California wine makers.
  - Research: notes and writing, 1992- 1993 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of research notes and preliminary writing on California wine makers.
  - Tchelistcheff, Andre, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of transparencies of winery where Andre Tchelistcheff consulted in Liguria, Italy. Also included are negatives from portrait session, a copy of California Wine Industry Oral History Project entitled” AndreTchelistcheff: Grapes Wine and Ecology” and information about Beaulieu Vineyard.
  - Trinchero, Robert, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of information on Sutter Home Winery, their newsletter and gift catalog. Also included is correspondence and photographs.
  - Wine auction (Box 35, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of information about Napa Valley's wine auction.
  - Winery brochures, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of brochures from Napa Valley's wineries.
  - Winemaker lists, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of lists of California winemakers and their support systems.
  - Winiarski, Warren, 1978- 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of information on Stag’s Leap Cellars, newletters, notes, clippings, correspondence, prints and photographs.
- Series 4: Miscellaneous projects and research (Acc # 2015- 010), 1987- 2014
  The materials consist of additional photography projects that Caddes completed over her career. Also included is research on Silicon Valley potentially in hopes of creating a sequel to Portraits of Success: Impressions of Silicon Valley Pioneers.
  - Bozeman, Montana, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    The materials consist of clippings, correspondence, maps, receipts and brochures from a trip toBozemna, Montanta. Caddes accompanied Steve Wozniak, his wife at the time and his mother to Bozeman Montana where he was honored at the Computer Museum as a Computer Pioneer alongside with Tim Berners-Lee, inventor of the World Wide Web and Ray Tomlinson, inventor of email.
  - Clippings: Andreessen, Marc, 2000-2012 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Clippings: Apple Computers (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Clippings: Apple Computers (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Clippings: Computer History Museum, 2010- 2011 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Clippings: Craigslist, 2005- 2006 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Clippings: Doerr, John, 1999- 2004 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Clippings: Facebook, 2007- 2012 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Clippings: Gates, Bill, 2005- 2014 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Clippings: Google, 2006- 2011 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Clippings: Health and technology, 2008- 2011 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Clippings: Intel, 2003- 2009 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Clippings: Jobs, Steve (Folder 1 of 2), 2008- 2011 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Clippings: Jobs, Steve (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Clippings: Kilby, Jack, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Clippings: Magazines (Folder 1 of 3), 2001- 2005 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Clippings: Magazines (Folder 2 of 3), 2006- 2009 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Clippings: Magazines (Folder 3 of 3), 2010- 2014 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Clippings: Miscellaneous, 2004- 2013 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Clippings: Pixar, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Clippings: Silicon Valley, 2007- 2013 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Clippings: Silicon Valley Pioneers, 1990- 2010 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Clippings: Venture capitalists, 2008- 2011 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Clippings: Wozniak, Steve, 2003- 2009 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1987- 2008 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1986- 2005 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Documents and photographs, 1978- 1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Erlich, Thomas, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of photographs, notes, correspondence and research regarding a portrait session with Thomas Erlich.
  - Friedman, Milton (Acc # 2009- 039), 2001 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of correspondence, notes, clippings and research for a portrait session with Milton Friedman.
  - Friedman, Milton: photographs (Acc # 2009- 039), 2001 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Ginzton, Edward, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    The materials consist of "Times to Remember: The Life of Edward L. Ginzton", a manuscript written by Ginzton about his life.
  - Intel, 1990- 1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    The materials consist of annual reports of Intel, notes, clippings and correspondence.
  - Miscelleanous files, 2004- 2007 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of correspondence, notes, brochures and research.
  - Miscelleanous photographs (Folder 1 of 2), undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Miscelleanous photographs (Folder 2 of 2), undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986- 1988 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Noyce, Robert: clippings and memorial, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Noyce, Robert: notes and writing, 1990- 2008 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Self portrait, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Success sequel, 1995- 2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    The materials consist of clippings, correspondence, notes, research and lists for a proposed sequel to Portraits of Success.
  - Rosse, James (Acc # 1991- 089), undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    The materials consist of photographs and negatives of James Rosse, former provost of Stanford University.
  - Sher, Byron, 1980- 1981 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    The materials consist of negatives, photographs, correspondence and clippings.
  - Stanford cassettes, 1984- 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    The materials consist of cassettes of interviews, Steve Harris on February 20, 1985 and Barney Oliver on February 22, 1985. Also included is James Joyce's Ulysses read by Robert Polhemus. Also included is a button that reads "Reagan Library- Just Say No!".
  - Stanford: Falk building, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    The materials consist of construction on campus of the Falk building which is the cardiology building.
  - Stanford: Peters and Montgomery, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    The materials consist of photographs and negatives of Tom Peters and David Montgomery teaching at Stanford in 1982 at the Graduate School of Business. They taught at the Executive Program for Smaller Companies. Tom Peters (1942-) is a business management author who wrote In Search of Excellence in 1982. David Montgomery is a professor of marketing at Stanford's Graduate Business School.
  - Stanford: Reed and Barton, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    The materials consist of brochures, negatives, photographs and correspondence.
  - Stanford: Sky and rooftops, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    The materials consist of negatives and photographs of rooftop of the Shy Building.